Sync:YTET-Vicky8800   -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
u'll be meeting with agents from the FAA,the NTSB and local police.
我一会要见来自FAA，NTSB 和当地警局的代表
Usually Booth handles those people.
通常都是Booth应付这些人
Plane crashes don't belong to the FBI.
飞机失事这事不归FBI管
Why not? FAA stands for "Federal Aviation Administration,"
为什么不？FAA意思是联邦航空局
the NTSB stands for "National Transportation Safety Board."
NTSB意思是国家运输管理委员会
That sounds federal to me,and FBI stands for Federal...
那听起来挺联邦化，FBI代表联邦调查局
Zack...
It's the third time in a row  we've investigated without Booth.I don't like it.
我们这已经是第三次没有和Booth一起 进行调查了，我不喜欢这样
Why? He mostly ignores you.
为什么？他可常常忽视你
Ignoring me is Booth's way of acknowledging my presence.
忽视我是Booth认可我存在的方式
It's a guy thing.
这是男人间的事
Here we are.
到了
Dr. Brennan
Brennan博士
Yes.
是的
I'm Ian Dyson with the NTSB.
我是NTSB的lan Dyson
This is my assistant,Zack Addy.
这是我的助手Zack Addy
At approximately 0400 last night,
昨晚大约凌晨4点的时候
a private jet with five passengers on board reported horizontal stabilizer trouble
一架载着5位乘客的私人飞机报告说 水平尾翼出了问题
200 miles southeast of Norfolk.
在Norfole东南200英里
Yeager Airport in Charleston tracked them for 30 minutes
Charleston的Yeager机场人员 追踪了他们30分钟
until they dropped off the radar screen at 0430.
直到他们4点30分从雷达中消失
The plane tried to make an emergency landing here
这飞机试着在这儿紧急迫降
when it clipped some trees and slammed to the ground.
它撞倒了一些树然后撞到了地面
We found another mostly intact body over near the trees.
我们在那边树的附近发现了 一具几乎完整的尸体
The rest is bits and pieces.
其他的就残缺不全了
What makes this one of our cases?
这为什么成了我们的案子？
I beg your pardon?
你说什么？
We're kind of special. We're elite.We don't sort through just any set of bodies.
我们有点特别, 是精英分子 不是任何尸体都需要我们出手
It was a State Department flight with a bunch of VIPs on board.
这是一趟州政府部门的航班 上面有很多贵宾
Is that special enough?
那够特别了吗?
I apologize if I've offended you.
如果冒犯了你, 我道歉
Usually,we have an FBI agent who mediates our interpersonal encounters.
通常，我们有一位处理这些 人际交往的FBI探员
We found another skull.
我们找到了另一片头骨
Two skulls.Those,uh,pieces are from two different skulls.
两片头骨, 嗯, 那是两片不同来源的头骨
I'll leave you super elite types to it.
那就让你们这些超级精英去测定吧
Zack,we don't need Booth to mediate our interpersonal encounters.
Zack, 我们不需要Booth来处理人际交往
Pilot,copilot,brings our count to six.
驾驶员，副驾驶，算来遇难者有6个了
Three mostly intact sets of remains,one partial and two fragmented.
有三具几乎完整，一具部分完整 另两具零散不堪
Obviously,bodies are burned to a crisp.
很明显，尸体已经烧焦了
No dermis,very little soft tissue,indications of high-impact trauma;
体无完肤，剩有非常少的软组织， 受到过高强度的打击伤害
burst fracture of the lower thoracic and lumbar vertebrae consistent
下胸椎和腰椎骨的爆裂性骨折
with injuries caused by the vertical impact of the falling aircraft.
与飞机掉落的垂直撞击引起的伤害一致
Should I keep talking as though you're paying attention?
我要假装你在听,继续说下去吗?
What do you make of this?
你觉得这是什么？
A femur fragment.
一片大腿骨碎片
No charring.
没有烧焦
You think this fragment doesn't belong to the plane crash.
你认为这碎片不是飞机上的
What are the odds?
这可能性有多大?
A crashing plane falling  directly on a human being?
一驾坠落的飞机直接撞到一个人身上?
One in... ten million.
千万分之一的概率
The information that I'm about to tell you must not leave this room.
我现在要告诉你们的消息绝对要保密
I am philosophically opposed to institutional secrecy in all its forms.
我基本上反对任何形式的保密机制
Fine. Get out.
好, 出去
Two Communist Chinese trade attaches were on that plane
当它坠毁时, 有两位中国共产党 贸易大使馆人员在那架飞机上
when it crashed--both high-ranking in party
两个人在党内都是高层人士
Well,obviously,we shot it down.
哦, 很明显, 是我们击落它的
The FAA and the NTSB can prove that it was an accident.
FAA和NTSB都能证明那是一场意外
Also on the manifest was an American businessman,
而且，在旅客名单上还有一个美国商人
a pilot and a copilot.Five people.
驾驶员和副驾驶, 共5个人
Dr. Goodman,we found six sets of human remains on that airplane.
Goodman博士, 我们在飞机上发现了 6具人体残骸
Not to mention three bone fragments which were not on the plane.
何况还有三块骨头碎片不是飞机上的
Is there any chance those bone fragments were on the plane?
有没有可能那些骨头碎片是飞机上的?
What,you mean as carry-on luggage?
什么，你是说像行李一样?
No,everything on the plane burned.They were untouched by fire.
不，飞机上的所有东西都被烧了 它们却没有
And forget about the bone fragments for the time being.
先别管那些骨头碎片了
The State Department is extremely anxious to find the identity of that 6th person.
州政府部门非常迫切的想知道机上 第6个人的身份
No one wishes this to become an international incident,
没人想让这成为一个国际性事件
therefore this is our only priority.
因此这是我们必须先要做的
I disagree.
我不同意
For the love of God,why?
上帝啊, 为什么?
Because the plane crash was an accident,bone fragments were not.
因为这架飞机失事是个意外 而骨头碎片不是
How do you know?
你怎么知道？
Zack found unusual cut marks.
Zack发现不寻常的切割痕迹
Cut marks congruent with dismemberment.
切割痕迹与肢解形成的一致
People,one hour ago,I received a call from the Secretary of State requesting
伙计们，一小时前我收到了 国务卿打来的电话
that the unidentified extra passenger be our first priority.
要求确认不明旅客的身份为当务之急
So,now politics are more important than murder?
因此，现在政治比谋杀更重要?
I'm not saying "please."I'm not being reasonable.I'm making the decision.
我不是在说"请"，我也不是要理智 我是在做决定
First and foremost,identify that six body.
首要而且是最重要的任务是 确定第6个人的身份
Got it,or you want me to explain again?
明白了, 还是要我再解释一遍?
I got it,okay?The plane goes down,kablooey.There's an extra body on board which
我明白了, 好了吧? 飞机出毛病掉了下来 多了一具尸体你却不真的在乎
you really don't care about 'cause you're more interested in these bone
是因为你对这些在地上
fragments that you found on the ground.
找到的尸骨更有兴趣
Exactly.
正是
Oh,this all you got?
噢，这就是所有你找到的?
So far.Piece of skull,chunk of vertebrae,part of a femur.
目前为止是的, 一片头盖骨碎片 一大块椎骨，一部分大腿骨
Not much to go on.
不够继续调查啊
These fragments come from a person who was hacked.
这些碎片来自一个被肢解的人
Hacked to little bits?
被肢解成小碎片?
No,medium-size bits.I'm not sure how it turned into little bits yet.
不，中等大小的碎片 我现在还不清楚它是怎么变成小碎片的
Okay,and I'm here why?
好的, 那我为什么到这来?
Dismemberment,little bits--it's a murder.
肢解成小块，这是谋杀
FBI doesn't have jurisdiction at a golf course.
FBI对高尔夫球场可没有管辖权限
--Well,who does? --I don't know.Try the PGA.
--那谁有? --我不知道, PGA(职业高尔夫球协会)吧
You know,you've done a couple cases without me and you miss me.
你知道的，你已经有好几个案子 没和我一起办了, 想我了吧
Zack misses you,not me.
Zack想你了，我可没有
Zack and I don't even talk.
Zack和我甚至没怎么说过话
He seems to think it's a male-bonding ritual.
他似乎觉得这是男人之间的默契
Maybe he's right.
可能他对了
--No,it's not. --Could be.
- 不，才不是 - 有可能
You told him that so you wouldn't have to talk to him.
你和他那样说, 所以你就不必和他说话了
Well,it was nicer than shooting him.
那总比开枪打他要好吧
Goodman has ordered me to investigate the other extra body.
Goodman已经命令我去调查那一具 多出来的尸体
Well,then you better get on that.Next time you know you miss me,
那你最好马上去做, 下次想我时
pick up the phone,call me.We'll do lunch or something.
拿起电话，打给我 我们可以一起吃午餐或是干点别的
I do not miss you.
我才没想你
--Come on. Say it! --I do not miss you!
- 得了吧, 说出来吧 - 我才没想你!
Dr. Brennan,Agent Booth,you have a visitor.
Brennan博士，Booth先生 有人找你们
--No,I don't. --Miss me.
- 不，我才没想你 - 你有想我
Dr. Temperance Brennan.
Temperance Brennan 博士
Yes.
是的
Special Agent Seeley Booth. I'm Jesse Caine.
Seeley Booth特别探员 我叫Jesse Caine
You're Jesse Caine?
你是Jesse Caine?
You've heard of me?
你听说过我?
I haven't.
我没有
Jesse here is sort of an expert on missing persons cases.
这儿的Jesse是失踪案的专家
I've done some writing on missing person laws and investigative techniques.
我写了一些失踪人口方面的法案 和调查方法的文章
Interagency cooperation,jurisdictional dispute,that kind of thing.
部门间合作，司法纠纷 诸如此类的东西
I heard about the bones you found at the golf course.
我听说了你们在高尔夫球场 发现尸骨的事
I can't really talk about that.
我不能和你谈论这个
I don't mean the Communist Chinese on the plane.
我不是指飞机上的中国共产党人
Communist Chinese?
中国共产党人?
The other bones,the fragments.
其余的骨块，那些碎片
How'd you hear about the Communist Chinese?
你是怎么听说中国共产党人的?
Those pieces of bone you found on the golf course?
那些你在高尔夫球场发现的碎片?
I'm pretty sure that's my dad.
我很确定那是我爸爸
My expertise in missing persons investigation derives from one thing
我这些寻找失踪人员的能力 源于一件事
my search for my father.
寻找我父亲
He went missing five years ago during a trip to his cottage in Virginia Beach.
他五年前在去弗吉尼亚海滩别墅途中失踪
What makes you think these bone fragments come from your father?
是什么使你认为这些碎片是你父亲的呢?
You know there is a question of national security here that is in my jurisdiction.
这儿有一个关于国家安全的问题 是在我的管辖之内
He's not supposed to know about the Chinese.
他不应该知道中国人的事
My investigations lead me to conclude
我的调查让我得出结论
that my father was murdered in the area and his body disposed.
我父亲被谋杀并抛尸在这地方
What do the police say?
警察怎么认为?
They gave up four years ago.
他们四年前就放弃了
Because there was no evidence of foul play.
因为没有证据表明那是犯罪事件
The investigation was bungled.The city police didn't have the manpower.
调查搞砸了 城里警察没有足够的人手
The state trooper said it was a federal matter
州警察说那是联邦政府的事
and you guys suggested a private investigator.
而你们建议私人调查
It was not bungled,okay?Because there was no evidence of foul play.
那没有被搞砸，好吗? 因为没有证据表明那是犯罪事件
It's a common story,okay?
这是很寻常的事，好吧？
A guy goes in for a pack of cigarettes,
一个男人去买一包烟
he ends up renting out snorkeling gear in Guam.
最后却租借了关岛的齿轮通气管
He doesn't know what it's like to lose a parent. You do.
他根本不知道失去父母是什么滋味 而你知道
You want back down a jot there,buddy?
你最好收回刚才说的话，伙计?
How do you know about that?
你是怎么知道的?
No offense,Dr. Brennan,but you're a writer,a well-known scientist.
没有冒犯的意思，Brennan博士 但是你是个作家，一个知名科学家
It's out there. Plus,you're one of us.
大家都知道, 另外, 你是我们中的一员
One of us?
我们中的一员？
People whose loved ones have simply vanished.In your case,both parents.
人们所爱的人就那么消失了 而你则失去了双亲
Okay,how do you know about the Chinese?
好吧，你是怎么知道中国人的事的?
Do not look at Dr. Brennan,okay?Whether you like it or not,
不要看Brennan博士，好吗? 不管你喜不喜欢
this is an issue between you and the FBI.
这是你和FBI之间的事情
If body parts are found in roughly the area my father disappeared,
如果尸体大概在我父亲失踪的地方找到
I'm going to know about it.
我就一定要知道
Radio chatter,the Internet,the local law enforcement...
广播，因特网，地方法律部门
That's all I'm prepared to tell you.
那正是我打算告诉你的一切
Do you mind if I ask you how many bone fragments you found?
介意我问问你发现了多少骨头碎片吗?
Yes,I do.I don't discuss ongoing investigations.
是的, 我介意,我不会讨论正在进行的调查
She doesn't discuss ongoing investigations.
她不讨论正在进新的调查
Fair enough,Dr. Brennan.
很好，Brennan博士
These are my notes from the last five years.
这是我五年前的记录
Every lead,every clue,every person I've ever talked with is here.
每一条道路，每一个线索 每一个人和我聊过的人, 都在这
And why would Dr. Brennan care about that?
为什么Brennan博士会在乎这些呢？
'Cause it will at least give her a candidate to eliminate.
因为它至少能让她除去一个怀疑对象
He's got a point.
他说的有道理
My father's medical records,pictures,last known whereabouts,
我父亲的医疗记录，照片 最后出现地点
even a connection to the golf course.
甚至和那个高尔夫球场的联系
Also my phone number.
还有我的电话号码
But don't worry.If I don't hear from you,you'll hear from me.
不过不用担心，如果你没给我消息 我会给你消息
Pushy.
真激进
Well,maybe he discovered that being pushy is how you get cops to pay attention.
或许他发现激进才能引起你们警察注意
What are you hawking at me for?
你这样顶撞我为了什么?
The Chinese,the plane crash,that's geopolitics.This is murder.
那些中国人. 飞机失事，那是政治 这是谋杀
Will you help?
你会帮忙吗?
Well,you know,I guess if you're really asking me I guess I could,you know,
你知道, 如果你真的求我 我想我会
budget with my boss to make it look like
去和我老板商量，使它看起来
it was attached to the Chinese plane crash thing.
是与中国人的飞机失事有关
We've made some progress on the mystery passenger.
那个神秘乘客的身份有一些进展了
Fill me in.
跟我说吧
Nasal ridges indicate she was a Caucasoid female,approximately five feet,ten inches
鼻梁骨的测定表明她是个高加索女性 大约5英尺10英寸高
Epiphysial fusion puts her age somewhere between 20 to 25.
骨龄测试估计她的年龄在20到25岁之间
I have a theory.
我有个想法
Femme fatale assassin.
致命的美人暗杀
Unregistered flight attendant.
没注册的空姐
Young beautiful girl,doesn't appear on the in-flight manifest,
年轻貌美的女孩 不在飞机的乘客名单上
group of high-powered politicos...
一群位高权重的政客...
What? What?
什么? 什么?
Someone on that flight might have been doing his daughter or his girlfriend a favor.
飞机上的某个人或许是帮忙 顺便载了他的女儿或是女友
You're so sweet,honey.You really are.
你人太好了, 亲爱的, 真的
You think she was the in-flight entertainment.
你觉得她是飞行中的娱乐
Anything you want to tell us about the bone bits you care about?
对于那些你所关心的骨块 有什么要告诉我们的吗？
Supra-orbital margin is rounded,suggesting a male.
眼窝的上缘是圆的，表明是个男性
Yes,and there's signs of osteophitic lipping or polish on this piece of vertebrae
是的，而且在这块腿骨有唇形变 (骨的病变)和发亮的痕迹
Arthritis?
关节炎?
So,middle-aged guy.
那么，是个中年男人
Weathering and discoloration suggests these bones have been
风化和退色表明这些骨块已经
out there for approximately five years.
在那大约有5年了
I'm going to ask you guys to help me on this.
我想让你们帮我一下
You mean,after the communist thing?
你指, 处理完共产党人的事之后?
No,immediately.
不, 马上
I'm in.
我加入
You want us to defy Dr. Goodman?
你想让我们违抗Goodman博士吗?
I'm in.
我加入
Not defy,per se.Do both jobs,but...but keep one a secret.
不是违抗, 应该说是两件事情同时进行 但一件保密
I'm in.
我加入
We get it. You're a rebel.
我们知道了，你是个反叛者
Zack,I need you  to analyze the cuts on the bone.
Zack，我要你分析一下骨头上的割痕
I was kind of hoping to keep my job.
我只是希望能保住工作
There's not enough skull here for me to do any reconstruction.
这儿没有足够的头盖骨让我进行重组
If I give you a picture,you could tell me if the skull piece doesn't match?
如果我给你张照片，你能告诉 我这些头盖骨是否匹配吗?
I could construct a schematic and
我可以建个示意图
see if the shard fit the general shape of the skull if I had a picture.
来看那些碎片是否匹配头骨的大概形状 如果有照片的话
Has anyone noticed that I was the first to offer help and apparently,I'm useless
有谁注意我是第一个愿意提供帮助的人 而显然，我没事做
Not true.You're the one that's going to keep Goodman from finding out.
不是的，你负责不要让Goodman 发现我们的调查
I'm in.
我加入
So the bone fragments are the same sex and age as my father.
这些骨片与我父亲的性别和年龄相符
Yes.
是的
Thank you.
谢谢
It's a long way from conclusive.
还要很久才能断定是不是你父亲
Yeah,I know at times like these not to get hopeful.
对，我知道像现在这时候不要充满希望
But,on the other hand,you've got to have hope.
但是，另一方面，你必须有希望
Even after five years?
即使5年以后?
People are found after decades,Dr. Brennan.
有些人数十年后才被发现，Brennan博士
After centuries.You've done some of the finding.
甚至是几个世纪后 而你已经有所发现了
Booth says you've made a living off of the disappearance of your father.
Booth说自你父亲失踪后 你就靠追踪他生活
About six months after my father disappeared,
我父亲失踪大约6个月后
I found out nobody was actually looking for him.
我发现实际上根本没人在找他
Next thing I knew,I was an expert in motivating the police-- victims' rights.
然后，我就变成了个推动警察 保护受害者权力的专家
Becoming well-known is a byproduct of my search for my father,not the goal of my search.
变成名只是我寻找父亲的副产品 并不是我寻找的目的
You should understand my motivation better than most people in law enforcement.
你应该比司法部门的人更了解我的动机
I'm not really interested in bonding over the loss of my parents.
我没兴趣在父母失去这件事上和你有联系
Booth is looking over your file now.
Booth现在正在找你的档案
I wasn't looking for his help.
我没有寻找他的帮忙
We work together.Booth knows that the bone fragments are evidence of foul play.
我们在一起工作，Booth知道 那些骨片是犯罪行为的证据
That's all the motivation he needed.
那就是他所要的动机
You didn't have to lean on him?
你不必偏袒他?
Not at all.
根本没有
If you say so.
如果你这么说的话
One of the bone fragments has distinctive  ridge-mark indentations.
这些骨块中一块有明显的隆起缺口
A knife mark.
一处刀痕
Yes. Specifically,a carving knife.
对，具体点是，一把雕刻刀
Well,what about the other ones?The jagged marks?
其他的呢? 那个锯齿形痕迹?
Some kind of machine blade.
一种机器的刀锋
What? Like a... a jigsaw or a chain saw?
什么? 像是...一把竖锯或是链锯?
Are you suggesting one of the Chinese diplomats was wielding a chain saw
你是说一个中国外交官挥舞着一把链锯?
good one,sir.Very droll.
很好，先生, 非常滑稽
Zack knows much more about this than I do,
Zack在这方面比我知道的要多
but we weren't discussing a literal chain saw cut,
但我们不是在讨论一个链锯割痕
but,rather,the pattern  it leaves on the bone.
而是那链锯留在骨头上的样式
Right?Zack?
对吧? Zack?
You know,blades move in several distinctive ways.
刀锋在骨头上有一些独特的移动方式
Several distinctive ways.
一些独特的方式
Circular,elliptical,segmente
圆形的，椭圆形的，线形的
Chain saws are designed to cut soft materials at high speed.
链锯是用来在高速下切割软材料的
When cutting hard materials like bone,they create wave-ridge walls
当切割硬物像骨头时，就会留下 由于刀锋的运动
by the action of the blade.This pattern's too organized. Too linear.
所留下的波浪型痕迹 这个样式太整齐了, 太线形了
Therefore,no Chinese Chain Saw Massacre scenario.
因此，没有什么中国链锯杀人狂
Yes. Fascinating.What has it go to do with the OXcts of the plane crash?
是的，令人惊奇 这和飞机失事有什么关系?
We not only have to reassemble each of the plane crash victims,
我们不仅要重组每个飞机遇难者的尸体
but figure out how their remains were scattered.
还要找出这些残骸是怎样分散开的
Not by being cut up. That's for sure.
不是被切开的，那是肯定的了
Now we've eliminated blades.
现在我们已经排除刀割了
Never freeze on me again.
别再对我发愣了
I find Dr. Goodman scary.
我发现Goodman博士很吓人
Well,I'm never trusting any of us again.We're that good at lying
好了，我不会再信任我们中的任何人了 我们都那么擅长说谎
We're going to do much better.
我们要做的更好
Well,you know,I have to admit
你知道, 我不得不承认
Jesse Caine's file on his father is both well-organized and complete.
Jesse Caine关于他父亲的档案 既有条理又完整
Yep. The main suspect is his father's girlfriend.
是，主要的嫌疑犯是她父亲的女友
--Karen Anderson. --No alibi.
- Karen Anderson - 没有不在犯罪现场的证明
And,since they were living together at the time of the disappearance,
还有，因为在失踪时他们一起住
she remains in the house,and has access to their joint accounts.
她就继续在那房子里 并可以使用他们的共用帐号
How much money are we talking about?
大概涉及多少钱？
Max Caine,he was a stockbroker.He was worth millions.
Max Caine, 他是股票经纪人 身价百万
But,you know,after seven years missing,the courts will declare him officially dead.
可是，你知道, 失踪了7年 法庭已经官方地宣布了他的死亡
By that time,she could have siphoned out most of the money.
那时候，她就可以取走所有的钱了
So I say we go visit Miss Anderson,and we'll know pretty fast if she's a suspect.
所以我说要去拜访这位Anderson小姐 很快我们就会知道她是不是个嫌疑犯了
How?
怎么办？
How?Subtle psychological indicators.
怎么办？微妙的心理变化
I looked those up on the Internet.
我在因特网上查过这些了
Body language,sweat,tonal quality,shifty eyes.
身体语言，汗，声调的变化 多变的眼神
Hey,you know what?
嘿，你知道吗？
I don't go poking around your bone stuff,okay? Just leave the human stuff to me.
我可不会管你骨头的事，好吗？ 就让我处理观察人方面的事
Why has Max's disappearance become a matter for the FBI?
为什么Max的失踪变成FBI的事情了?
Max's disappearance is not an FBI matter.
Max的失踪不是FBI的事情
You're an FBI agent.
你是个FBI探员
Human remains were found in the course of a federal investigation.
在联邦调查过程中有人的残骸被发现
Agent Booth is tasked with the job of identifying them.
Booth探员的任务就是确定他们的身份
I'd like to eliminate Max Caine as a possibility,and just move on altogether.
我希望能排除Max Caine的可能性 总之继续调查
So this is a  pro forma interview?
所以这是一个形式上的访问?
Yes. Yes. Absolutely.
对，对，当然
Because I know Max's son Jesse accuses me of Max's murder.
因为我知道Max的儿子Jesse 控告我是害Max的凶手
Why do you think he suspects you?
你为什么认为他怀疑你呢?
Because of the age difference between me and Max.
因为我和Max之间的年龄差距
Because I'm still living in the house.Because,after five years,
因为我仍旧住在这房子里 因为5年以后
I dared to fall in love with someone new. And who knows?
我又爱上了别人, 谁知道呢?
Well,some people find it harder than others to get over the loss of a loved one.
嗯，失去挚爱的人后 有些人恢复要比别人难得多
Bones?
What?
什么?
Jesse got to you,didn't he?
Jesse打动你了, 是么?
The dimples and the sad smile and melancholy,on a mission to find his beloved father.
脸上带酒窝有着悲伤微笑 寻找挚爱父亲的忧郁男子
You know all that.
你知道的
Jesse didn't love his father?
Jesse不爱他的父亲?
Max and Jesse didn't speak for the two years before Max disappeared.
Max失踪前2年里和Jesse 根本没有说过话
And that was before I came into his life.
而且是我遇到他之前
What do you think caused the rift?
你认为是什么导致他们父子不和?
Max cut Jesse off financially.
Max不给Jesse生活费
Max thought Jesse was lazy,running around New York doing nothing with his life and
Max觉得Jesse很懒惰 和一帮朋友在纽约无所事事
well,Jesse was furious.
Jesse为此很生气
The hack marks were caused by a Heidel carving knife.
砍痕是把雕刻刀留下的
And the osteological profile suggests evidence of postmortem freezing.
骨骼轮廓显示出他死后曾被冰冻
Maxine disappeared midwinter.
Max是在冬天失踪的
What about the jagged cut marks
那锯齿状的痕迹呢？
This is the part that makes me queasy.
这就是让我作呕的原因
The victim was frozen,dismembered,and fed into a wood chipper.
受害者被冰冻, 肢解 然后被丢进了削木机
Then spread over a golf course.
撒了高尔夫球场一地
Either talk loudly enough so I can hear all the way,or whisper so I can't.
你们要么说响点好让我听到 要么就小声点我听不到
Maybe,if we told Goodman what we know,he would authorize a change in priorities.
也许我们告诉Goodman我们了解的 他会对优先权作个改动
Or he'd suspend us all for defying him.
或者他会因为我们忽视命令让我们停职
Angela's right.
Angela说的对
So we're going to drop this,
那么我们不干这个
and get back to what Dr. Goodman told us to do in the first place
重新开始做Dr. Goodman 一开始让我们做的
No. We are going  to keep doing what we're doing behind Goodman's back.
不, 我们要在背地里继续
That's the spirit!
这才对!
It's true.My father cut me off financially.
是的, 我父亲不给我生活费
So I take it that means you talked to Karen.
你见过Karen了
Anything else you failed to mention?
你还有什么没有和我们说的么?
Why didn't you tell us?
你为什么不告诉我们?
I know I didn't kill my father,
我知道我没有杀我父亲
so I'd rather you didn't waste your time on that line of investigation.
所以我希望你们 不要把时间花在这条线索上
Too late. So what happened between you and your father?
太迟了, 你和你父亲到底发生了什么?
About five years ago,I was enrolled at NYU.
五年前, 我进了NYU
But all I really did was go clubbing and have a good time.
但我真正做的只有去酒吧玩乐
My father was right to cut me off.
我父亲不给我生活费是对的
I was a disappointment to him.
我让他失望了
But if only he could see you now.
只有当他看到你现在这样他才会失望
I like to think he can see me now.
我很希望他能看到我
Your father is dead.
你父亲死了
A dead person can't see anything.
死人什么都看不见
Maybe that's true.Maybe it isn't.
也许是, 也许不是
But,either way,at least I know my dad would be proud.
至少我知道我父亲会很骄傲的
Bones?Tell Jesse what happened to the victim.
Bones? 告诉Jesse受害者是怎么死的
Really?
要说吗?
What?
什么?
It's just that usually you tell me not to tell people.
这种时侯你经常不让我说的
Well,it can't be worse than some of the things that I've imagined.
起码不会比我想象的要糟糕吧
The victim was frozen,dismembered,and fed through a wood chipper.
受害者被冰冻, 肢解 然后丢进了削木机
Bones is checking out what type of wood chipper was used
Bones在查用的是哪种削木机
and we're going to trace it to the manufacturer and see if one was sold in Virginia Beach.
我们会询问生产商去判断 Virginia海滩是否有出售
I can't believe someone would do that to my dad.
我不能相信有人会对我父亲做这种事
We haven't positively identified the victim as your father.
我们还没有确认被害者就是你父亲
I have our artists comparing the skull fragment to pictures of your dad.
我们找艺术家将头骨碎片 和你父亲的照片进行了对比
Could I see the bone fragments
我能看下碎片吗?
This is all of him?
这就是他所有的了?
Yes.I mean,it's all of somebody.
是的, 是某人所有的
He was a big man,my dad.
我父亲很高大
It's hard to believe that this is all that's left of him.
很难相信这就是他所剩的了
How can you get anything from three small bits of bone?
你怎么做到从 小小三片骨头里找线索的?
It's more than a lot of people get.
这已经比很多其他人所剩的要多了
I know where my dad was right before he disappeared.
我知道我父亲失踪前在哪里
I know my dad met with a client at the North Star Grill in Virginia Beach.
我知道我父亲在Virginia海滩的 North Star Grill见了客户
I know he had meat loaf.
我知道他吃了肉条
I know he was supposed to meet Karen at the pier,but he didn't show up.
我知道他和Karen约好在码头见面 但他没有出现
I know she waited two days before reporting him gone.
我知道她过了两天报警
I have a good timeline,and I have three small bits of bone.
我有时间表, 而且我有三块小骨头
You don't have any of those things,
你什么都没有
and I realize how hopeless you must feel.
这让我发现你有多么绝望
Come with me.
跟我来
This is all you have?
这是所有的了?
Yes. You were right about how little it is.
是的, 你说它们少说对了
No,I mean this is simply your copy of the official file.
我是说这只是官方文件的复印件
Yes. What else would there be?
是的, 还有什么资料呢?
You never tried to hire any private investigators?
你从没有雇过私家调查员吗?
Did any poking around by yourself?
所有都是你自己在干?
Well,I'm pretty new at field work.
我对实地侦察很生疏
Mostly been a lab rat my whole career.
我的职业生涯都在实验室里
Plus,I trusted the authorities would do what the could.
而且我相信官方会尽全力去查
The authorities have rooms filled with files like these.Warehouses.
官方的仓库里堆满了这种东西, 货舱
I'm the authorities.Booth is the authorities.
我是官方的人, Booth也是
Did you ever show this file to Booth?
你给Booth看过这个吗?
No. No.
没有
This is where I work.
这我工作的地方
Which is my cue.
那是我的台词
Angela,come in.This is Jesse Caine.
Angela, 进来, 这是Jesse Caine
Hello. Hi.
你好
Hi. Angela ntenegro.
你好, Angela ntenegro
What's that?
这是什么?
nothing that can't wait.
不是什么要紧的
Is it about my father?
和我父亲有关吗?
You know,as far as I know,which is quite far,believe me,
据我所知道的, 相信我
no one has tried to kiss Brennan in this office and lived to tell about it.
在这个办公室里试着亲Brennan的人 没有一个还活着的
--Angela. --Would one of you please tell me what that piece of paper is?
- Angela - 你们能不能告诉我那张纸是什么?
It's a,It's a schematic
这是个示意图
comparing a skull fragment we found on the golf course to pictures of your father
高尔夫球场的头骨和 你父亲照片的对比
And?
然后?
It doesn't not match your father.
和你父亲不是不相符
So it could be him?
所以可能是他?
Yeah. There's a pretty good chance.
有很大几率是他
I knew it.
我就知道
Are you hooking up later?
你过后和他一起吗?
I didn't arrange anything.
我什么都没安排
--Why not? --Because you were right there,hovering.
--为什么不?  --因为你就在旁边, 转来转去
I was not. I was... being your wingman.
我没有, 我只是你的后援而已
What's that?
什么?
I was rendering assistance and enabling where needed.
我在旁边是为了以防万一好出手相助
Booth thinks he might be a suspect.
Booth觉得他嫌疑很大
Oh,now you're just looking for excuses not to get involved.
你现在在找不被牵扯进去的借口了
Plane crash victim number four,Captain Jacob Howard.Pilot,age 47.
4号空难受害者, Jacob Howard机长 飞行员, 47岁
Height five foot six.Weight approximately 167 pounds.
5英尺6英寸高, 大约167英镑重
Overlay the photograph.
把照片重叠上去
Frontal zygomatic sutures line up.Cranial menengies are in synch.
前^骨成一直线 头盖骨部分也符合
Excellent. That's one more off our list.
很好, 还剩一个人
Victim number five,Shenru Fong.Age 56.
5号受害者, Shenru Fong, 56岁
Height five foot six,weight approximately 140 pounds.
身高5英尺6英寸, 重140英镑
Yes,yes,that's terrific.Except,we knew all of these people were on the plane.
很好，现在知道所有这些人都在飞机上
What the State Department wants to know is the identity of our mystery woman.
州政府部门想知道的是神秘女人的身份
I hope I can count on your full energies on this,Dr. Brennan.
我希望你全身心投入在这个上 Brennan博士
If I could be completely honest,sir.
其实, 老实说...
Toxicology reports came back from all six victims.Pilot and copilot were clean.
6个受害者的毒药报告 说明驾驶员和副驾驶都没中毒
Our two Chinese nationals had elevated levels of alcohol and Sildenafil,
两位中国人体内有很高浓度的 酒精和Sildenafil(性功能障碍药)
more commonly known as Viagra,
就是熟知的Viagra
and our mystery girl showed traces of alcohol and cocaine.
神秘女孩体内也有酒精和可卡因
So will the cover-up start now,or somewhere between here and the State Department
掩饰过程是现在开始呢  还是报告到州政府部门之前再开始？
You were saying about being completely honest?
你刚才说老实说什么?
Yes,sir.Regarding the bone shards.
就骨头碎片来说
The prostitute was six inches taller than anyone else on the flight,
妓女有6英尺, 比机上的人都高
and she had occupational stress markers.
她有职业性的标志
Let's not call her a prostitute yet,Mr. Addy.
Addy先生, 暂时不要叫她妓女
What occupational markers?
什么职业性的标志?
Ah,it's a foot thing.
是脚上的
She was a fetishist?
她是个恋物癖?
Both her cuboid and medial malleolus show signs of wear.
她的骰骨和锤骨中段都有磨损
You can relax,Dr. Goodman.She wore extremely high stiletto heels.
放松点Goodman教授 那是因为她穿超高跟的鞋子
I reconstructed her face from the partial skull.
我从部分头骨还原了她的脸
She was hot.
她很性感
What's our next move?
你们下一步打算怎么做?
I suggest we try to match this reconstruction with escort ads
我建议把这张脸与陪航广告进行比对
both Internet and print in the DC area.
DC区域内的网上和书面版本
Oh,I'll do that.
我来做这个
Was that overly enthusiastic?
会不会太积极了?
Thank you for the update.
谢谢情况汇报
This case continues to be your top priority,correct?
这还是你们优先考虑的, 是吗?
If I could suggest..
我是想说..
Dr. Brennan has been very clear about your priorities on this,sir.
Brennan对优先很清楚
What's that?
这是什么?
The only Black Mantis wood chipper in Virginia Beach.
Virginia海滩唯一一台 Black Mantis牌削木机
I subpoenaed the records fromhe manufacturer
我把记录传票给生产商
and traced it back to the town equipment yard.
找到了小镇供应处
My people,they,couldn't find any blood residue.
我的人找不到血迹残留
That makes sense,if the corpse was frozen.
如果尸体被冻住了就不会有血
not to mention this puppy here has ground up about 10,000 trees,you know.
这条小狗狗还切割了1万棵树
Hey,I figure you can match the blades to the cuts on the bones,right?
你们可以把刀和骨头上的痕迹 进行对比, 不是吗?
Or do something I haven't thought of much more,u know,confusing and scientific.
或者做些我想不到的事 很深奥和令人费解的
Booth. Nobody told me you were working this case.
Booth, 没人告诉我你处理这个案子
Only two people have had access to this machine in the past seven years
过去7年里只有两个人用这台机器
city maintenance foreman and a maintenance worker by the name of Sparks
城市维修监工和维修员Sparks
Sparks has got a jacket,so,what do you say,You want to come with me to go talk to him
你想和我一起去和他谈谈吗？
Told you. It's a guy thing.
我告诉过你, 这是男人的默契
Yes,I'd like to come.
是的, 我去
All right,here we go.
好吧, 走吧
Let Angela do the escort matching.
让Angela做陪航的对比
I have something a lot more interesting for you and Hodgins.
有些更有趣的事要你和Hodgins做
What's more interesting than escorts?
还有什么比陪航更好玩?
I need you guys to run a dispersal pattern test on the chipper.
我要你们用这个削木机 做个分散类型测试
Using what medium?
用什么东西?
Assume the victim was frozen solid when he was fed into the chipper.
想想受害人被扔进去的时候是冰冻的
No way!
不可能
The correct response would be,"Yes,way."
正确的回答是“是”
Oh. Yes way.
是
You ignore Zach and make him think you've got some special bond.
你一直忽略Zack 让他觉得你们有某种特殊联系
Yeah,but it works,doesn't it? I'm happy,he's happy.
但是这很有效不是吗？ 他开心我也开心
It's not the truth.
不是这样的
But it works.
但这很有效
Ray Sparks,I'd like to have a word with you,please.
Ray Sparks, 我想和你谈谈
Zach wants to fit into the real world more than anything.You're not helping.
Zach比任何人都想适应社会 你在帮倒忙
FBI. Special Agent Booth.
FBI, 特别探员Booth
He went around the back.
他从后面逃了
No,no. The other way,Bones.
不不, 另一边, Bones
FBI. Freeze.
FBI, 不许动
Ray Sparks.
Ray Sparks
Hey,I didn't do nothing wrong!
我什么错事都没有做!
I feel like kicking him.
我想踢他
That's normal after a pursuit,which i should do that.come on.
这在追赶后很正常, 我会这么做的
Too many people.How we going to keep this from Dr. Goodman?
人太多了 我们怎么向Goodman博士隐瞒?
he's having lunch with the president of Harvard.
他在和Harvard校长吃午饭
What's going on?Why is every guy from the Jeffersonian out here?
发生什么了?  为什么所有Jeffersonian的人都在外面?
They're scientists.This is a fascinating scientific inquiry.
他们都是科学家 这是个有趣的科学实验
Oh,my God.
我的天
They're all out here because you're going to feed something through this wood chipper.
他们都出来是因为你们要把某个东西 扔进这个木材粉碎机
Not just something.A frozen pig.
不是某个东西, 是一只冻猪
The morphologyrpf pig bones is almost identical to human bone.
猪骨的形态和人骨差不多
By feeding the pig through the wood chipper,
把猪丢进粉碎机里
we'll be able to deterhe dispersal pattern of the fragments.
我们可以确定分散状态
By comparing the pulverized pig's remains
通过将猪碎片
to the fragments we foundwe at the golf course,
和在高尔夫球场找到的碎片对比
we'll be able to tell if this is the actual wood chipper the victim was fed through
我们可以确定 这是不是被害者丢进的粉碎机
Liars.You just want to see what happens when you toss a frozen pig into a wood chipper.
撒谎, 你们只是想看看当你们把一只冻猪 丢进粉碎机后会发生什么
Ready?
准备好?
One!Two!Three!
1..2..3..
Okay,what have we got here?Break and enter,assault,drunk,disorderly.
Ok，什么事来着? 入屋爆窃，殴打 酗酒，妨碍治安
I been keeping myself out of trouble for the past four years now.
从四年前我就一直让自己远离这些问题
How long you been a maintenance worker for the city of Virginia Beach?
你在维吉尼亚沙滩做维修工人多久了
Since '92.
自92年开始
You ever meet a guy by the name of Max Caine?
你认识一个叫Max Caine的男人？
No.
不
Karen Anderson?
Yeah,I know her.
我认识她
How?
怎样认识
She bartends at the golf course.
她在高尔夫球场里做调酒师
You don't strike me as a golfer,Ray.
Ray, 我不觉得你打高尔夫
City land is right across the creek from the course and I,
工作的地方就经过高尔夫球场而我
I go to the clubhouse a couple times a week to have lunch.
我一星期会一两次去那里的会所吃午饭
Hey,how'd you pay for that house you live in,Ray?I mean,that's pretty nice
嘿，Ray你怎么负担得起你现在住的房子 我是说，它挺不错的
You got a hard time sticking to one time ago?My mom left me the house.
你以前有过一段很艰难的日子吗? 房子是我妈留给我的
She left it to me and my brother Frank.Five years ago.
她五年前把房子留给我和我哥Frank
Five years ago Max Caine disappeared,Karen Anderson's boyfriend
五年前aren的男朋友Max Caine失踪
so,you know,you can see how my suspicions might be a little aroused.
所以, 你明白我现在对你更怀疑了
Yeah,but the thing is...I didn't live in Virginia Beach five years ago.
是，不过事实是 五年前我不住在维吉尼亚沙滩
I was in Southampton Correctional Center...
我当时在南汉普顿改过中心……
doing six months for skipping out on a DUI warrant.
因被判酒后驾驶, 服刑6个月
Guess I don't need a lawyer,right?
我想我不需要律师，对吧
There's no way that wood chipper experiment was connected
这次削木机实验不可能
to the plane crash at the golf course.
与这次高尔夫球场坠机事件有关
--Look... --Don't say anything.Just listen.
- 是这样的... - 不要说，只需要听
Your primary job is to do as I say.Failing that,your job is to fool me.
你主要的工作就是按照我安排的 失望的是，你的任务是欺骗我
You failed to fool me,Dr. Hodgins.
你不能欺骗到我，Hoogins
I'd have fooled you if you'd gone to lunch as planned.
如果你按计划吃午饭我就骗到你了
I'll find some administrative ways to punish you.
我将会用一些行政手法惩罚你
Parking,dining room privileges,budget reviews,that sort of thing,
停车，餐室特别"照顾" 重检预算诸如此类
but if it happens again...
但是如果再发生...
I got it.
我明白了
No. You don't.
不, 你不明白
You think I'm a kind and fair man.
你认为我是个公正善良的人
Egoless,balanced,ruled by intelligent reflection.
不自私，稳定的，理智处理事情
But I do have an ego.I can be vindictive and petty.
不过我也是自私的 我可以是小气记仇的
I will take you down,
我会打击你
even if it means striking at you through your friends and coworkers.
哪怕这意味着将通过打击你的朋友 和合作排挡来对付你
Now you understand.
现在你明白了
Ray Sparks was in jail when your father disappeared.
你爸爸失踪时Ray Sparks在坐牢
He might have acted as a go-between,put Karen in touch with the hit man.
他可能是Karen和那个行凶者的中间人
One of the things that you lecture about
在你写的东西里其中有一个
is that the simplest theory usually turns out to be true.
最简单的推测经常都被证明是真
Usually,not always.
"经常"，不是"总是"
What's the simplest theory in this case?
在这事件里什么是最简单的推测？
Disowned son realizes that his father may remarry,lose his inheritance.
被断绝关系的儿子认识到父亲可能再婚 同时也将失去继承权
Booth,are you accusing Jesse of murdering his own father for money?
Booth,你现在是指控Jesse因为钱 而杀害自己亲生父亲？
You ever hear of the Menendez brothers?
你有没有听说过梅斯迪氏兄弟的事？
I came to you about the bone shard,saying it might be Dad.
我来到这里是告诉你有关骨头的事情 说它有可能是我父亲的
Hey,look,your father is declared dead,
瞧，你父亲是被宣告死亡
you get your inheritance before Karen Anderson spends it all.
你要在Karen把遗产花光前 得到你的继承权
You don't seem too upset about the accusation.
你似乎对被指控一点都不伤心
Agent Booth,for four years I've been making enemies with law enforcement.
Booth探员, 我已经与强制性法令为敌四年了
Attacking me is a pretty typical response.
抨击我是很典型的反应
Booth,is this one of those times when you just poke and prod to get reactions?
Booth,你是不是用刺激别人来得到反应？
Now,listen,Bones,we have to treat him like a suspect.
听我说，Bones， 我们必须以对待嫌疑犯来对待他
He is not a member of the team.
他不是你们中的一分子
Look.I'm like you.I need the truth.
我和你很像，我需要真相
I have to get back to the lab.
我得回实验室
Satellite imagery of the golf course.
高尔夫球场的卫星图片
These three dots show where the bone fragments were found.
这里三个点表示发现骨头碎片的地方
Can you show me the results of the wood chipper test?
可以给我看削木机的实验结果?
The "V" shape indicates the maximum distance from the point of origin
这个"V"形状表示 从起点开始的最远距离
a bone fragment could have traveled given similar wind speeds and ambient temperatures.
一片骨头碎片可通过相近的风速和室温 到达的地方
Okay,and remove the plane crash.It's irrelevant to this.
Ok，移开这些飞机碎片 它和这无关系
The question is...
问题是...
in order to use the guys' pig-grinding experiment,
为了用他们磨碎猪的实验
where do we place the wood chipper
我们要把削木机放哪里
I bet the murderer...aimed the wood chipper over the stream.
我认为凶手...把削木机放在溪流上
So the evidence would wash away.
这样可以冲走证据
What's that?
这是什么？
That is...a small access road for maintenance vehicles.
这是...一条为维修机器设的小捷径
Try putting the wood chipper there.
试把削木机放在那里
Sweet smell of success.
哈哈, 接近成功
We should see if we can find any more bone fragments here and here.
我们应该在这里和那里看 能不能找到其它更多的骨头碎片
Are we any closer to identifying our mystery woman?
我们是不是接近 辨认出那位神秘女士呢？
I'm not... I'm not certain.
我不...我不确定
Brennan is still waiting for an update.
Brennan还在等着更新
I saw you come in,sir,and I have an update.
我看到你进来 而且我有最新消息汇报
I have a list of possible matches on our geisha in the sky.
我有一份可能是 我们那位空中艺妓的名单
She is Caucasian.Our mystery woman is definitely Caucasian.
她是高加索人 我们那位神秘女士肯定是高加索人
We've sent a list to the FBI and they're checking it out.
我们已经把名单 发给FBI并且他们正在跟进
Well,in that case,you might wanna turn your attention back to the bone fragments
好的，这样你们或许想把精力 转回到那骨头碎片的事
I came for the file on my parents.
我来是为了我父母的档案
You think I might have killed my father.
你认为我把我父亲杀死了
No,it's just...
不是，只是...
I asked the wrong person to help me,and...
我找了不适合的人帮忙而且...
What?
什么?
I just don't think it's healthy,what you're doing.
我不认为你现在做的事是健康的
Putting your whole life into this.
把你的生命都放到这事情上
And I suppose the way you're doing it,
而我认为你正在用的方式
putting nothing into solving the disappearance of your parents,
没有解决处理你父母的失踪
I suppose that's healthy?
我该认为这是健康的?
We're searching the golf course for more bone fragments.
我们正在高尔夫球场里 寻找更多的骨头碎片
Amazingly,we found a piece of finger with the nail still attached.
惊奇的是 我们发现一手指上仍贴着指甲
And underneath that nail...
在指甲下...
Polyurethane. The tough stuff.
聚氨脂类, 强韧的物体
The victim must have been scraping at something before he died.
受害者肯定在死前曾经抓过些什么
I can't identify this bone anomaly.It's full of osteoids. It's Thick.
我不能辨认出这畸形骨头 它充满着骨状，很厚
Maybe part of the mandible.
也许是下颚骨的一部分
Human. Something odd with the cell structure.
伙计，细胞组织有点奇怪
Wood chipper wouldn't do damage at the cellular level.
削木机不可能制造这样的细胞级损伤
It's a nonmalignant bone tumor.
这是良性骨癌
I need the most recent bone scans from Max Caine's medical records.
我需要看Max Caine的体检里 最近时间的骨头检验
Hodgins.It's Booth.
我是Hodgins, 是Booth
The locals justarrested Jesse for attacking Karen Anderson.rs
地方检察官检控Jesse故意伤害 Karen Anderson
that Jesse showed up at Karen's house to confront her.
Jesse在Karen家前出现和Karen对质
He was ranting about the murder of his dad.
他怒吼他父亲被杀害的事
Eddie tried to throw him out,but the two of them,they exchanged punches...
Eddie尝试赶他走 但是这两个人互相推撞
The fact that Jesse confronted him doesn't mean that he isn't the killed.
事实上Jesse在他面前说 并不代表他不是凶手
I know.
我知道
You know what? He might have done this just to make us
你知道么, 他可能这么做
think that he was angry at her.All right,he's smart.
让我们认为他对她很生气, 他很聪明
No poking and prodding-- do you think Jesse murdered his father?
没有任何刺激，你认为Jesse会谋杀 他的父亲吗？
No,Bones,all I'm saying is we get into these things,
不, Bones, 我现在说的是我们处理事情
we look into murders,we can't let our heartstrings get all plucked,okay?
我们追查凶手，我们不能让我们 心里面的感觉溜走，好么?
We got to poke at people's wounds,we're gonna make them bleed a little.
我们戳开人们的伤口 我们让他们流点血
We got to make them tell us things that they normally wouldn't want to tell us.
我们要让他们告诉我们 他们原本不会告诉我们的事情
We got to be willing to be hard on them,is what I'm trying to say--
我们要乐意去为难他们，这是我要说的
even when we know that we're no different than them.
就算当我们知道我们和他们没分别
You didn't answer my question.
你没回答我的问题
Well,I have a opinion. You want to know?
好的，我是有我的想法, 你想听啊?
If I had to bet,I'd say he didn't do it.
如果要我打赌, 我会说他没有这么做
--Me,too. --I'm going off my gut.I mean,what's persuading you?
--我也是  --我没辙了，我说，是什么说服你的?
The bone fragments at the golf course,they didn't come from Max Caine.
在高尔夫球场找到的骨头碎片不是 Max Caine的
That's great-- you knew that when you asked me what I thought.
很好, 你问我的想法之前就已经知道
You testing out my instincts,Bones?
你在试探我的直觉，Bones?
Poking and prodding.I learned from the best.
刺激一下, 我从最厉害的人学的
It's not my dad.
那不是我父亲
No. We don't know who it is yet.
不, 我们还不知道它是谁
How can you be certain?
你怎么确定能确定
We found a juxtacortical chondroma.A nonmalignant bone tumor.
我们发现下颚骨的肿瘤组织 一个良性的骨瘤
Your father's X-ray showed no sign of such a tumor.
你父亲的X光检验显示他没有这样的肿瘤
Maybe he got it after the X-rays.
可能他是在照完X光后才有
The X-rays were taken two months before he disappeared.
X光检验是在他失踪前两个月做的
It's a slow growing tumor.It would have taken...
它是慢性肿瘤，它需要...
years to get to the size and density that we found.
数年的时间才形成我们找到的样子
Look,I'm gonna see if I can get this assault stuff to go away and get you out of here.
我去看看我能不能搞掂这殴打事件让你出去
I'm sorry,Jesse.
我很抱歉，Jesse
For what?Suspecting that I killed my own father.
为了什么? 怀疑我杀害我亲生父亲?
No. I'm not sorry for that.
不，我不是为这而道歉
I know what it's like not to know what happened.
我明白不知道过去发生些什么 是什么感觉
I know how painful that can be.
我知道那有多痛苦
And I'm sorry for you.
而我为此对你觉得很遗憾
If the bones don't belong to Max Caine,who's our dead guy?
如果这些骨头不是Max Caine的 那是哪个人的?
We can send out a description of the chondroma to area hospitals,
我们可以把这些肿瘤组织的描述 发给当地附近的医院
see if it leads to any missing patients.
看是不是有失踪的病人
Yeah,we can do that.List the pertinents.
是，我们可做，列出有关的
Me? Are you talking directly to me?
我? 你是直接对我说话吗?
you can tell because my eyes are looking at you,my mouth is aimed in your direction.
你可以这样认为因为我的眼睛正看着你 我的嘴巴是向着你这个方向
But what about our guy thing?
但是我们男人间的事呢?
If you're speaking to me,then does this mean I'm not on the team?
如果你是对我说话 那么是不是意味着我不是在组里？
Zack,let's concentrate on the work.
Zack, 我们还是专注工作
Pertinents.
有关的
The victim died,we don't know how.
受害者死了，而我们不知道他怎么死
He was then frozen,dismembered with a Heidel carving knife
他当时是被冷冻，被雕刻刀肢解
and pushed through a Black Mantis 1200 wood chipper.
并且被扔到一个Black Mantis 型号1200的削木机
The exact wood chipper you fed the frozen pig through.
正是那个你们放冻藏猪进去的削木机
The exact wood chipper that Ray Sparks had access to.
正是那个Ray Sparks拥有的削木机
But Ray Sparks was in jail.
但Ray Sparks是正在坐牢
Ray was in jail when Max Caine disappeared.
当Max失踪时Ray是正在坐牢
But our victim isn't Max Caine.
不过我们的受害者不是Max
Well,who else would Ray Sparks have motive to kill?
好那还有谁Ray Sparks有动机去杀害？
--The victim is a middle-aged male. --His brother.
- 受害者是中年男人 - 他哥哥
What motive?
什么动机?
They both inherited the house.Okay,you guys,you look at the tumor,
他们共同继承了房子 你们继续查看骨头的肿瘤组织
and Bones and I will go talk to Ray. Come on.
而Bones和我就去找Ray, 快来
While you're there,look for a large freezer.
当你到那里，查一下有没有大型的冰箱
Why?
为什么?
The body was frozen.
受害者是被冷藏的
Polyurethane is a common insulating liner in freezers.
聚氨脂是一种常用于冰箱的物料
We found it under the victim's fingernail,like he was scratching to get out.
我们发现在受害者的手指甲下有 好象他曾经抓，试着出去
The detectives who picked up Sparks say
抓获Sparks的侦探说
he claimed his brother was alive and well last time he saw him.
Sparks宣称自己的哥哥 在他上次见面的时候还活得好好的
well,he might have been for about 30 minutes,until he ran out of air in here.
他可能被关在这里有30分钟 直到他窒息
My guys,they found claw marks on the inner linings on both sides.
我的人发现在里面两边的隔板 有搔抓的痕迹
What kind of person could lock a living human being in a freezer?
什么样的人会把活人关在冰箱里?
Who is there?
那是什么？
That's a fingernail.
手指甲
His own brother.
他亲生的哥哥
Booth got you out.
Booth放你出来
1,200 bucks bail,and a promise to stay away from Karen and Eddie.
1,200保释金 还有永不接近Karen和Eddie的承诺
We solved the case.
我们解决案件了
And I'm sorry,it's not your father.
另外，我很抱歉，那不是你的爸爸
We identified the victim.His name was Frank Sparks.
我们已经辨认出受害者 他是Frank Sparks
I'm sorry I couldn't help you,Jesse.
我很抱歉我不能帮你
How do you live with it?
你是怎么生活下去的?
What,the disappearance of my parents?
什么?, 我父母失踪?
The fact that nobody's looking.
是没有人在找寻他们的事实
I never thought about it that way until I met you.
在我认识你之前我从来没有想过这
There's a Zen koan.
禅学说
It says that if you want to find something,you have to stop looking.
它说在你想寻找到某样东西 你必须停止找寻
I can't do that.
我做不到
My dad's watching,and I don't want to disappoint him again.
我父亲在看着我，我不想再让他失望了
Even if you don't believe it,
就算你不相信
I know your parents are somewhere proud of what you do.
我知道在某地方, 你的父母为你而骄傲
It's not rational,but...I love the thought of that.
这不理智，但我还是喜欢这样的想法
How'd Jesse take it?
Jesse怎么样了?
Like an orphan.
像个孤儿
What?
什么?
That's just... That's a little poetic for you.
这是...你说的有点诗意
I didn't mean it that way.
我不是那个意思
I want to ask you a favor.
我想请你帮个忙
Oh,geez. Another favor.
噢，老天，又一个帮忙
I wonder if you wouldn't mind taking a look at this.
我想知道你介不介意看一下这个
The file on your parents?
你父母的失踪档案
Okay.
好吧
You want to think about it?It's a pretty big favor.
你不用考虑一下吗？这是个很大的帮忙
You'd do it for me.
你也会这么帮我的
Yeah,I would.
是的我会
I'm proud you asked,Temperance.
我很骄傲你要我帮忙
Dr. Brennan.Angela wants to know if we should order anything for you.
Brennan博士, Angela问要不要帮你点餐
no,I'm not staying. Thanks,Zack.
不，我不留, 谢谢你, Zack
Guess we caught another one,right?All for one and one for all?
我想我们又抓到一个人了, 对吧？ 一劳永逸?
I'll take a look and see what they didn't give you and I'll get back to you,okay
我会好好看看有什么他们没有给你 到时再联系你，好么?
Back to annoying Zack?
又忽视Zack了?
All right,look,I know you don't approve,but,you know,
我知道你不赞成, 但是你要明白
it works for us.It worked for him,so...
这对我和他都有效，所以...
I get it.And it... It's kind of sweet.
我明白, 这...有点贴心
well,your people are my people.
你的人就是我的人
I have people ?
我有人?
hey,I have people.
嘿，我有人
Sync:YTET-Vicky8800    -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 风从指间滑过, Marcella, Vicky怪 校对: Sybil 时间轴:Vicky8800